wespeke.com 2016-11-29

# WeSpeke | Privacy Policy

Last updated: September 29, 2012. 

#### Introduction 

This Privacy Policy outlines the policies and procedures used by Wespeke, Inc. (“Company") for the collection of personally identifiable information. As outlined in the Terms on this Web Site, Company provides services to allow you to develop a registration profile and make it available to the public. Company will collect, use and disclose information provided through our Web Site by you and others only in the ways disclosed in this statement. This statement applies solely to information collected at Company's Web Site. Company reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If Company makes any material changes to this Privacy Policy, you will be notified by means of a notice on Company Web Site. 

#### Information Collection

Company collects information through our Web Site at several points as provided by you at creation of your profile, including but not limited to name, address, email address, education and employment history. By accessing the Web Site, either through registered account or through your Facebook account, you expressly accept the Terms and this Privacy Policy. You agree to allow registered users to view your profile and the information contained in your profile. You also allow third parties to view limited information contained in your profile. As outlined in the Terms, Company cannot be responsible for information or updates provided by users of the Web Site. Throughout the time period that your profile remains active, you will be permitted to access, update, modify, revise or close your account. Company may retain modified information as required under its programs, but will not make such modified information available unless you allow otherwise. Company will not provide information to third parties without your consent, unless required by law. However, as outlined in the Terms, the information included on your profile is available for public view. 

Company also collects the following general data that is not personally identifiable information such as progress through site content, time spent online, and progress in language proficiency. Company may also retain the content of and metadata regarding any correspondence you may have with Company or its customers and third party users, regardless of the mode of communication by which such correspondence was made. By way of example, Company may collect and store information related to clicks through the Web Site, text exchanges with users on the Web Site, text input into the Web Site, gaps in user sessions and search match results. Company collects this information through tracking of the content accessed and used by the user. You expressly consent to the collection and storage of this information when you register your profile with Company. Company will record certain audio content to ensure compliance with its Terms because Company is committed to safety and security of its users. This information also assists Company in improving the Web Site and the materials, products and services that we offer on the Web Site, and to more effectively and efficiently respond to both current and future inquiries. 

To gather additional information, Company may use cookies, which are small text files that Company's Web server places on your computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. Cookies enable Company to track usage patterns and deliver customized content to users. Our cookies have an expiration date. Our cookies collect personally identifiable information. This information is stored on your computer. 

#### Children's Privacy

Company is committed to protecting the privacy of any child/children that utilize Company products, services, materials and content. As such, Company does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register with the Web Site in accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and its Rule. By registering with the Site, any parent or legal guardian will be required to acknowledge and agree that such parent or legal guardian entitled to consent on behalf of your child/children. 

#### Information Usage

The personally identifiable information provided by you and collected by Company is entirely voluntary on your part. Company will allow other Web Site users to view your profile. Company will allow third parties to view limited information contained in your profile. As outlined in the Terms, Company cannot be responsible for information or updates provided by users of the Web Site. We will supplement information collected at our Web Site with data from other sources. If our policy on information collection or uses changes, we will post such changes at this location. Company may provide aggregate data, which does not include personally identifiable information, to third parties at Company's sole discretion. 

#### Access to Information

You will access your own personal information and maintain the ability to review for inaccuracies and update the contents of your profile. Upon registration or entering the Web Site through your Facebook account, Company will allow Web Site users parties to view your profile. As outlined in the Terms, Company cannot be responsible for information or updates provided by users of the Web Site. You must, at all times, abide by the terms of the Terms and the then-current Privacy Policy. This includes respecting all intellectual property rights that may belong to Company or third parties. You must keep your username and password confidential and not share it with others. Any violation of the Terms may lead to the restriction, suspension or termination of your account at the sole discretion of Company. 

#### Data Storage and Security

Company protects user information with the following security measures: 

User information on the server is accessed through the use of a registered account or by logging in using your Facebook account, establishing a session. The internal user ID is never used to communicate between browser and server, rather a disposable session identifier. The password is stored in an encrypted form on the server. All personally identifiable information exchange between the user's browser and Company's servers is encrypted using Secure Socket Layer encryption (SSL). Audio and video chats among users are direct between their browsers. All server ports are closed except for the standard HTTP protocol ports. 

In order to help secure your personal information, access to your non-public information is password-protected. To protect any data you store on our servers, Company regularly t_reviews its system for security purposes. However, Company cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Company that is provided on your profile. There is no guarantee that information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of the Company's safeguards. It is your responsibility to protect the security of your non-public profile information. 

#### Survey Serving Technology

The WeSpeke mobile app uses Pollfish SDK. [Pollfish](https://www.pollfish.com/) is an on-line survey platform, through which, anyone may conduct surveys. Pollfish collaborates with Developers of applications for smartphones in order to have access to users of such applications and address survey questionnaires to them. When a user connects to this app, Pollfish detects whether the user has enabled his Device’s interest-based-ads settings (Advertising ID for Android/Advertising Identifier for iOS). If not, Pollfish does not proceed to any action and cannot offer any survey to the user or collect any of his/her Data. If the user has enabled such settings, a specific set of user’s device data and response meta-data is automatically sent to Pollfish servers. These data will be associated with your answers to the questionnaires. By downloading the application you accept this privacy policy document and you hereby give your consent for the processing by Pollfish of the aforementioned data. Furthermore, you are informed that you may disable Pollfish operation at any time by (a) enabling the “opt out of interest-based advertising” in your device Settings area or by (b) [using the Pollfish “opt out section” available on the Pollfish website](https://www.pollfish.com/optout). We invite you to check Pollfish's [respondent’s terms of use](https://www.pollfish.com/terms/respondent), if you wish to have more detailed view of the way Pollfish works.

APPLE, GOOGLE AND AMAZON ARE NOT A SPONSOR NOR ARE INVOLVED IN ANY WAY IN THE DRAWS OFFERED BY POLLFISH. NO APPLE PRODUCTS ARE BEING USED AS PRIZES.

#### Questions

If any questions or comments with your profile arise, you should contact Company immediately via email at [support@wespeke.com](mailto:support@wespeke.com). We are committed to resolving disputes quickly.
